A Guide to the Records of the University Events Office, 1956-2007
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Records of the University Events Office 1956-2007
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
RG 6-9A
9 Hollinger document cases.
The collection contains records from events coordinated by the Events Office. It also contains brochures, posters, flyers and calendars information from various activities, conferences, and workshops dating from 1956 to 2007.
University Events Office
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Part of this collection was donated by the Office of Institutional Advancement. Other portions were collated by Dr. Robert C. McClelland and Benjamin Franklin Clymer.
Historical Information
The University Events Office plays a major role at Old Dominion University. It primarily organizes and plans various events all over campus, such as the President's Lecture Series, Commencement and Founders' Day. In the past, the University Events Office was part of the Office of Institutional Advancement.
Scope and Content
The collection contains records from events coordinated by the Events Office. It also contains brochures, posters, fliers and calendars from various activities, conferences, and workshops dating from the 1956 to 2007. Of interest is the list of ODU slogans submitted for Pride Day, 1993.
Contents List
- Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, and Institutes. 1956 - 1992
  This series contains papers dating from various conferences and workshops, dated 1956 to 1992
  chronological
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1956-1969 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1970-1976 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1977 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1978 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1979 (Box-folder 2:1)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1980 (Box-folder 2:1)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1981 (Box-folder 2:3)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1983 (Box-folder 2:4)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1984 (Box-folder 2:5)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1985 (Box-folder 2:6)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1986 (Box-folder 2:7)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1987 (Box-folder 2:8)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1988 (Box-folder 2:9)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1989 (Box-folder 2:10)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1990 (Box-folder 2:11)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1991 (Box-folder 2:12)
  - Conferences, Workshops, Seminars, Institutes 1992 (Box-folder 2:13)
- Calendar of Events 1962- 1981
  This series includes papers from events such as the President’s Lecture Series, Commencement, Board of Visitors’ Meetings, Founders’ Day, and Faculty Awards.
  - Calendar of Events 1962 - 1963 (Box-folder 3:1)
  - Calendar of Events 1963 - 1964 (Box-folder 3:2)
  - Calendar of Events 1964 -1965 (Box-folder 3:3)
  - Calendar of Events 1965 - 1966 (Box-folder 3:4)
  - Calendar of Events 1967-1968, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 3:5)
  - Calendar of Events 1969-1970, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3:6)
  - Calendar of Events 1974-1975, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 3:7)
  - Calendar of Events 1976-1977, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 3:8)
  - Calendar of Events 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3:9)
  - Calendar of Events 1979-1980 (Box-folder 3:10)
  - Calendar of Events 1980-1981 (Box-folder 3:11)
- University Events 1961 - 2007
  - Dedication of Campus Buildings 1961 - 1980 (Box-folder 4:1)
  - The Masquer’s Dramatic society of Norfolk College of William and Mary Programs 1962 (Box-folder 4:2)
  - Misc. Events 1962 - c 1988 (Box-folder 4:3)
  - Film Series 1969 - 1980 (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Interplay & Miscellaneous Art Events 1969 - 1970s (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Misc. Events 1970s (Box-folder 4:6)
  - Black History Month 1977- 1986 (Box-folder 4:7)
  - Faculty Awards 1979 (Box-folder 4:8)
  - Founders Day 1980s (Box-folder 4:9)
  - Misc. Events 1980s (Box-folder 4:10)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day Celebration 1986-1989 (Box-folder 4:11)
  - Waldo Lecture 1988 (Box-folder 4:12)
  - Arts, Literature 1990s (Box-folder 4:13)
  - Lectures & Panel Discussions 1990s (Box-folder 4:14)
  - Misc. Events 1990s (Box-folder 4:15)
  - Awards Events 1990-1991 (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Founders Day 1990-1991 (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Awards Events 1993 (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Black Instructional Faculty 1993-94 (Box-folder 5:4)
  - Board of Visitors Meeting 1993 (Box-folder 5:5)
  - Bus Tour 1993 (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Faculty & Classified Hourly Staff Party 1993 (Box-folder 5:7)
  - Founders Day 1993 (Box-folder 5:8)
  - Misc. Events 1993 (Box-folder 5:9)
  - Presidents Lecture Series Dan Quayle 1993 (Box-folder 5:10)
  - Presidents Lecture Series 1993-94 (Box-folder 5:11)
  - Pride Day 1993 (Box-folder 5:12)
  - Webb Center Opening 1993 (Box-folder 5:13)
  - Awards & Retirement 1994 (Box-folder 5:14)
  - Baskets for Books 1994 (Box-folder 5:15)
  - Board Reunion Dinner 1994 (Box-folder 5:16)
  - Board of Visitors 1994 (Box-folder 5:17)
  - Actor’s Regional Theatre 1990 – 2002 (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Bus Tour October 1993 (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Student Activities Council Movies poster undated (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Commencement 1994 (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Founders Day 1994 (Box-folder 7:2)
  - International Symposium 1994 (Box-folder 7:3)
  - Monarch Gardens Dedication 1994 (Box-folder 7:4)
  - President’s Box – Basketball 1994 (Box-folder 7:5)
  - President’s Council 1994 (Box-folder 7:6)
  - Presidents Lecture Series 1994-95 (Box-folder 7:7)
  - Teletechnet Demo 1994 (Box-folder 7:8)
  - Waldo Lecture 1994 (Box-folder 7:9)
  - Awards Events 1995 (Box-folder 7:10)
  - Board of Visitors Reunion Dinner 1995 (Box-folder 7:11)
  - Board of Visitors 1995 (Box-folder 7:12)
  - Career Advantage Press Conference 1995 (Box-folder 7:13)
  - Founders Day 1995 (Box-folder 7:14)
  - HBCU Tour 1995 (Box-folder 7:15)
  - Misc. Events 1995 (Box-folder 7:16)
  - Presidents Council Dinner 1995 (Box-folder 7:17)
  - Presidents Lecture Series 1995 (Box-folder 7:18)
  - ODU Promotional Lit 1995 (Box-folder 7:19)
  - State of the University Address Breakfast 1995 (Box-folder 7:20)
  - Wall 1995-96 (Box-folder 7:21)
  - Lucy Wilson Reception 1995 (Box-folder 7:22)
  - Basketball 1996-97 (Box-folder 7:23)
  - Board of Visitors 1996 (Box-folder 7:24)
  - Presidents Lecture Series 1996 (Box-folder 7:25)
  - Pre-Commencement 1996 (Box-folder 7:26)
  - Conferences, Forums, Debates, Symposiums – NATO 1998 (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Illumination 2000s (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Miscellaneous Fliers 2000s (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Founders’ Week 2000- 2005 (Box-folder 8:4)
  - ODU Spring Events 2000-2007 (Box-folder 8:5)
  - A Tribute to the Kochs 2001 (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Founders’ Day and opening of Ted Constant Convocation Center 2002 (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Colonial Encounters March 18-24, 2007 (Box-folder 8:8)
  - Misc. Events undated (Box-folder 8:9)
  - The Honorable Edythe C. Harrison Event ca 2001 (Box-folder 9:1)